All right, we're ready to start our fire.
What I always like to have nearby is my blower, just in case it needs a little extra air and oxygen to get moving.
I don't think its going to be an issue today since we've got a nice little bit of wind coming at us.
And that speaks to the next point of wich area should you light first.
Well, you should light all around the fire, two, three, four spots if you can.
But what we want to do is we want to light where the wind is coming from because that's going to give us a better chance of getting it catching fire, catching all of it on fire.
Maybe we won't have to light it in different spots around.
You'll actually be able to tell once you actually get it in there and get it lit.
So I'm going to go ahead and dip down here, and hopefully you can see this.
And I'm just going to light it, and it might take a couple of times to get the lighter going.
But you see you can insert these a lot further, rather than having a hand held lighter and trying to get your hand in there.
Or even using matches and throwing those.
And these tend to work better.
We'll go ahead and see if its not too windy.
We've got a flame in there.
It looks like its catching.
Can definitely see smoke, and where there is smoke there is fire.
Hopefully you can see the smoke on there, and it looks like it is catching real well .
And make sure that you stand outside of the line of the smoke, you wouldn't want to be breathing in the smoke.
So here we've got the startings of our bon fire.